{
    "subject": "resource/N.W.A",
    "predicate": "ontology/associatedBand",
    "object": "resource/J._J._Fad",
    "human_readable": "N.W.A was associated with J.J.Fad.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9671489596366882,
            "question": "Who was associated with J.J. Fad?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.925757884979248,
            "question": "What genre of music was associated with N.W.A and J.J. Fad?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.888448178768158,
            "question": "What was the nature of the relationship between N.W.A and J.J. Fad?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8822414875030518,
            "question": "What impact did the association between N.W.A and J.J. Fad have on their respective careers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7980428338050842,
            "question": "In what decade did N.W.A and J.J. Fad gain prominence?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7943233251571655,
            "question": "How did N.W.A's music differ from J.J. Fad's style?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7879425883293152,
            "question": "Who is J.J. Fad?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7594377398490906,
            "question": "Are there any other notable collaborations between N.W.A and artists like J.J. Fad?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4127529263496399,
            "question": "What group was N.W.A known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2875312864780426,
            "question": "Was N.W.A connected to any other musical acts?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=N.W.A was associated with J.J.Fad.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5630_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What group was N.W.A known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5630_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other notable collaborations between N.W.A and artists like J.J. Fad?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5630_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is J.J. Fad?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5630_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5630_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5630_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5630_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5630_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5630_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5630_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5630_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5630_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5630_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5630_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that N.W.A was associated with J.J. Fad. The documents mention that J.J. Fad toured, collaborated and socialized with N.W.A during the period recounted in the movie \"Straight Outta Compton\", and that they were considered as one of the first females to break through in a mostly male dominated rap genre, which was also associated with N.W.A."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that J.J. Fad was signed to Ruthless Records and had connections with N.W.A members, indicating an association between the two groups."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}